<!-- PCL Features library component -->
<library path="lib/libpcl_ros_features">
  <class name="pcl/BoundaryEstimation" type="BoundaryEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      BoundaryEstimation estimates whether a set of points is lying on surface boundaries using an angle criterion. The
      code makes use of the estimated surface normals at each point in the input data set.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/FPFHEstimation" type="FPFHEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      FPFHEstimation estimates the Fast Point Feature Histogram (FPFH) descriptor for a given point cloud dataset
      containing points and normals.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/FPFHEstimationOMP" type="FPFHEstimationOMP" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      FPFHEstimationOMP estimates the Fast Point Feature Histogram (FPFH) descriptor for a given point cloud dataset
      containing points and normals, in parallel, using the OpenMP standard.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/SHOTEstimation" type="SHOTEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      SHOTEstimation estimates SHOT descriptor for a given point cloud dataset
      containing points and normals.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/SHOTEstimationOMP" type="SHOTEstimationOMP" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      SHOTEstimationOMP estimates SHOT descriptor for a given point cloud dataset
      containing points and normals, in parallel, using the OpenMP standard.
    </description>
  </class>
  
  <class name="pcl/MomentInvariantsEstimation" type="MomentInvariantsEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      MomentInvariantsEstimation estimates the 3 moment invariants (j1, j2, j3) at each 3D point.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/NormalEstimationOMP" type="NormalEstimationOMP" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      NormalEstimationOMP estimates local surface properties at each 3D point, such as surface normals and curvatures,
      in parallel, using the OpenMP standard.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/NormalEstimationTBB" type="NormalEstimationTBB" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      NormalEstimationTBB estimates local surface properties at each 3D point, such as surface normals and curvatures, in
      parallel, using Intel's Threading Building Blocks library.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/NormalEstimation" type="NormalEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      NormalEstimation estimates local surface properties at each 3D point, such as surface normals and curvatures.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/PFHEstimation" type="PFHEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      PFHEstimation estimates the Point Feature Histogram (PFH) descriptor for a given point cloud dataset containing
      points and normals.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/PrincipalCurvaturesEstimation" type="PrincipalCurvaturesEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      PrincipalCurvaturesEstimation estimates the directions (eigenvectors) and magnitudes (eigenvalues) of principal surface 
      curvatures for a given point cloud dataset containing points and normals.
    </description>
  </class>

  <class name="pcl/VFHEstimation" type="VFHEstimation" base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
    <description>
      VFHEstimation estimates the Viewpoint Feature Histogram (VFH) global descriptor for a given point cloud cluster dataset
      containing points and normals.
    </description>
  </class>

</library>
